camerakings.com 2010-02-09

# CameraKings

CameraKings Privacy Policy

At CameraKings, we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Your Private Information will never be disclosed to anyone and will be used for business purposes only. All orders are placed through a secure online server. We Use **VeriSign** a trusted third party to assure your security. Only Authorized persons have access to your information.

Data Security and Protection

We guarantee that every online transaction you make will be 100% safe. This means you pay nothing if unauthorized charges are made to your card as a result of shopping at our online store. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your bank cannot hold you liable for more than $50.00 of fraudulent charges. If your bank does hold you liable for any of this $50.00, we will cover the entire liability for you, up to the full $50.00. We will only cover this liability if the unauthorized use of your credit card resulted through no fault of your own from purchases made while using the secure server. In the event of unauthorized use of your credit card, you must notify your credit card provider in accordance with its reporting rules and procedures. We also make every effort to ensure that your purchase experience at CameraKings.com is secure. We use state-of-the-art data encryption technology to protect against loss, misuse or alteration of your user information. Secure Socket Layers (SSL) encrypt the information sent between your computer and our database. In addition, we use Internet fraud screening to protect credit card transactions.   
To be sure you're browsing secure pages, check your Web browser's status bar (located at the bottom of the window) for the closed padlock icon. This icon appears in the latest versions of Internet Explorer and Netscape Navigator to tell you that you are viewing a secure web page. Also, all browsers display an "s" after the "http" (https://…) in the Web site address to indicate that you're in a secure environment.  
We also protect your purchase by preventing the shipment of merchandise to a fraudulent address. All billing addresses are verified electronically and all alternate shipping addresses are verified manually. Any customer shipping to an address that differs from the billing address must put this alternate address on file with his or her credit card company. We then call the credit card issuer to verify that the customer has indeed put the information on file. If your uncomfortable ordering online you can always order by telephone, toll free 1-866-277-6257.

Confirmation, Pricing and Availability:

We make every effort to get your order to you as soon as possible. In-stock items are generally shipped within 24 to 48 hours after confirmation. If there is a problem with your order you will receive an email stating more details. Items shipped by UPS Ground may take longer, depending on your location. Special and Custom orders may also take longer to process. Ask our Customer Service Representatives for shipping details when you place your order.

Information Collected

When you shop on our site, we collect personal information from you such as your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product selections, credit card or other payment information. We may also collect, or our third party ad server and content server will collect the URL you came from, IP address, domain types (e.g. .com or .org, etc.), your browser type, the country, state and telephone area code where your server is located, the pages of our site that were viewed during a visit.

How Information is Used

We do not sell or rent your personal information to others. We use customer information we collect only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, enhancing the operation of our site, for statistical purposes and to administer our systems. We may use third parties to help us fulfill orders, to help process payments, to provide customer service, to serve site content, to help administer promotional emails, and to administer warranties purchased. We give them access to the information needed to complete their job. Sometimes that includes a portion of your personal information. Our computer systems protect personal information using an advanced firewall server technology.

Cookies

We use cookies to help identify you when you visit our store and to customize your experience. The cookie contains a randomly assigned user identification number, the country where you are located, and we may track where you came from, and how you browse our site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies. We do not disclose your personal account information or any information about your purchases to anyone.  
When you leave our site, we are no longer responsible for protecting your privacy. We suggest your review the policies of the new site. These other sites may use their own "cookies", collect data or solicit personal information from you. Please be advised CameraKings is not responsible for the privacy policies and guidelines on these sites.  
CameraKings reserves the right to modify this policy at any time.
